http://www.zonnewind.com/cookie-policy/

Home > Cookie policy
Our website makes use of cookies. These are small (temporary) text files for your PC, so you do not have to enter or download the same information over again. Handy, right? Cookies give us insight on how you use the website and provide us with pointers on how to improve its usability. We also use cookies for marketing purposes to display information that is relevant to you.
Accepting cookies
If you want to make use of our website in the most optimal way, it is necessary to accept the cookies. Accepting is super simple, all you have to do is click ‘agree’.
No appetite for cookies?
Are you not interested in cookies whatsoever? Then you can also disable them in your browser. However, our website will not work optimally. Click on one of the browsers below for further explanations on how to disable cookies.
Chrome
Firefox
Internet Explorer
Edge
Safari (iOS)
Safari (macOS)
Which cookies do we use?
As soon as you visit our website, this will be saved. What that means for you is that you do not have to re-enter your information when filling in a contact form, should you have to reload the session. Your information will not be shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Functional cookies
This ensures that our website works optimally and that you can place products in the shopping cart and proceed to checkout. Without these cookies these functions could not work.
Purpose of functional cookies
This is where the temporary information of your website visit is stored. As a result, you do not have to re-enter your details into a form, should the page reload or in the case that you have not filled in all the fields correctly.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen. The data will be deleted after each session.
Name of the cookie
PHPSESSID
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Comparing products
We also use a cookie to compare products within the webshop. This service cannot work without these cookies.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen or from our webshop. This data will be deleted after each session. Name cookie: comparison_selectedProducts
Sharing information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Video reviews
The purpose of this cookie
Viewing video reviews on YouTube is made possible by this cookie. This cookie ensures that we can gain a better understanding of the advantages and disadvantages of a product.
Features
This is a cookie that comes directly from Youtube. This cookie will only be deleted after seven months. Names cookies: VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE and use_hitbox
Sharing of information
Youtube does share information with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Cookie notification
The purpose of this cookie
This cookie is used to remember whether you have closed the cookie notice or not. Without this cookie it would not be possible to close the cookie.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen. This data will be deleted after each session. Name: cookieBar
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
User recognition
Purpose of these cookies
By using these cookies, we are able to know whether you are logged in and which shopping basket is yours.
Features
These cookies come from Zonnewind Zeilreizen and are removed after 6 months. Name: Session, Secure, Clone-Token, SecureCookieClone-Token
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Language recognition
Purpose of this cookie
This cookie will remember your language selection and prevents you from having to select the language on our website or webshop each time anew.
Features
These cookies come from (company name) and are removed after one year. Name: locale, seenLanguageSwitcher
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Analysis cookies
These cookies collect information about how our website is used by its visitors. We use this information to improve the website. It also allows us to show information that is relevant to you. This way we can continually improve our products and services.
Google Analytics
The purpose of these cookies
Google Analytics allows us to measure how you use our website or webshop. We utilise this information to improve the website. Without this cookie we do not have access to your data and we can not make continuous improvements.
Features
This cookie is from Google and will be deleted after a maximum of two years. Names utma, utmb, utmc, utmv and utmz.
Sharing of information
Google does not share anonymous data with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Partner websites
Purpose of this cookie
Our partner sites such as Google Adwords or Kieskeurig will forward you to our website or webshop. This cookie ensures that we get access to this data, which allows us to make improvements on our sites. Without this cookie we have no access and it takes longer for improvements to be made.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen. After 30 days, this data will be deleted again. Name: Partner
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Search function
Purpose of this cookie
Imagine that one mouse click will provide you with all information that is relevant to you. This saves you a lot of time and trouble. This cookie ensures that you see all this relevant information. We use the resulting data to improve the search engine.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen. After a maximum of 1 year, this data will be deleted again. Name: spkr
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Viewport
Purpose of this cookie
This cookie ensures that the resolution, with which you visit our website, is forwarded to Google Analytics. We then analyse this data to determine which resolutions are most commonly used by our users. Based on this data, we can optimise the sites.
Features
This cookie comes from Zonnewind Zeilreizen. These data will be deleted again within 15 minutes after the visit. Name: viewPort
Sharing of information
Your information is not shared with third parties. Please read our privacy statement for more information.
Marketing cookies
These cookies are used for marketing purposes. This way we can send you information or offers that are indeed applicable to you.
Double-click
Purpose of this cookie
This cookie keeps track of the pages you view. Based on this data, we show you relevant advertisements on our partner sites. We keep track of how often the advertisement has been shown to you, whether you have clicked on it or if you have placed an order. Without this cookie we cannot show you any personal offers and you will miss out on this information.
Features
This cookie comes from Google and will be deleted after a maximum of 18 months. Names: id, _drt_, __gads
Sharing of information
Google shares this information with third parties. Please also read our privacy statement for more information.
Remarketing
Purpose of this cookie
Google Analytics provides us with insight on how you use our website or webshop. Based on this data, we can show you products that suit you or that you are interested in. Without this cookie, this is not possible and you miss out on this valuable information.
Features
This cookie comes from Google and is deleted after a maximum of two years. Namur: utma, utmb, utmc, utmv and utmz
Sharing of information
Google does not share this information with third parties. Please also read our privacy statement for more information.
Twitter
Purpose of this cookie
This cookie tracks which products you are viewing. This way we can show you relevant information or advertisements on Twitter.
Features
This cookie comes from Twitter and is stored for up to 2 years. Names: guest_id, twid, muc
Sharing of information
Twitter does not share this information with third parties. Please also read our privacy statement for more information.
Facebook
Purpose of this cookie
This cookie from Facebook tracks which products you are viewing. This way we can show you relevant ads on Facebook. Without these cookies, you miss out on personalised offers.
Features
This cookie comes from Facebook and will be stored for up to 2 years. Names: lu, xs, s, presence, act, c_user, csm, p, fr, datr
Sharing of information
Facebook does not share this information with third parties. Please also read our privacy statement for more information.
Advertising cookies
Third parties will be given the opportunity to place advertising cookies on our website or online store. On the other hand, we also place advertising cookies on third-party sites. We can combine the data that results from this. We keep track of which advertisements you have viewed, the frequency thereof, whether you have clicked on the advert and whether you have made a purchase. Based on this information, we can identify your interests in certain ads and adjust the ads we show to you accordingly. We also do this on the websites of third parties. We do this in order to be able to present you with the most relevant offers, based on your surfing behaviour, search behaviour and buying behaviour.
Advertising networks and media agencies act as intermediaries for webshops and advertisers. The advertising cookies of these parties allow us to show you advertisements from third parties.
